

According to my Diploma, I'm a economist. I've been working credit risk for over 10 years. It helped me to develop communication skills, attention to detail, ability to analyze data sets, manage software services. However, the world, as well as technologies, is changing really fast and I also want to improve myself.

I'd like to work in a good IT company in a position of QA/QC engineer. I believe I can do it, because in my previous job I dealt with identifying and correcting mistakes, writing some documentation and reports, and I had to use my organizing skills. I'm sure the job is interesting and promising. It inspires to know that you can be a part of creating something useful and awesome.

Name: Andrii Borovskyi **Position**: QA/QC engineer Level: Trainee/Junior Phone: +380679684185 Email: Anderson @ukr.net

Linkedin: linkedin.com/in/andrii-borovskyi-0ba619207

Github: github.com/Andrii147

Languages:

Ukrainian - Native **Russian** – Native **English** – Intermediate

SKILLS

Development Tools

- Jira
- Microsoft SQL Server Management Studio
- **TestRail**
- Trello
- Selenium IDE
- Fiddler
- Postman

RDBMS

- PostgreSQL
- MySQL

Programming Languages/ Technologies

- Technical Documentation/ SRS
- HTML/CSS
- JavaScript/ES6+
- **JSON**
- Python (learning the basics)
- ReactJS/Redux

Methodologies

- Agile, SCRUM
- Kanban
- **TDD**
- XP
- V-model
- **Automated Tests**

WORK EXPERIENCE

As far as I am applying for the position of a trainee/junior, I have no commercial experience directly to the IT company.

But in my previous job, I worked as a project manager (product owner) in the big start-up online credit project. I was in charge of the task-setting, priority and urgency of the task, the timing and the correctness work of programme support.

I have practical and successful experience of testing and starting a large project, writing test-cases, and constantly working on creating, testing and starting new versions of the program.

Risk manager Flexible Financial Solutions, LLC

Dec. 2018 – Dec. 2020 Region Kyiv, Ukraine

Head of credit analysis Companion Finance, LLC Dec. 2014 - Now. 2018 Region Kyiv, Ukraine

Credit Decision Verification Center VTB Bank, PJSC Jul. 2012 – Apr. 2014 Region Kyiv, Ukraine

Education

Academy of Housing and Public Utilities Faculty of Enterprise Economy Specialization: Economist (Ukrainian) 1.09.1999 - 30.06.2004

Additional courses (online)

Course "JavaScript", BeOnMax, 2021.

Course "English language", January to now

Course "SQL and PostgreSQL for Beginners", BeOnMax, 2021. Course "The complete Python course for beginners", BeOnMax,

2021

Course "QA/QC engineer", Tommy University, 2021.







